I thought it was hi-versive.
Scary.
I like to make date-style videos of myself,
I like to make date-style videos of myself, and then edit them myself,
That's all there is to it.
So, are you going to M-1?
No. Can you do that?
Yes, I can. Really.
I'm sure of it.
I'm really proud of it.
It's a place where I can beat the other members,
When they came to see me at the concert, they said, "You were here today,
I was told that I was on this side of the stage today.
The kettle and the idol
I am the kettle of Starlast's middle class upbringing.
Let's have a look at today's guest!
This is my idol.
Hello.
I'm Akane Sora from Ukka.
Pleased to meet you.
We have Akane Sora from Ukka.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Actually, we're recording right now in the middle of red.
It's raining heavily outside.
Thunder is rumbling.
We may suddenly hear strange noises during the recording.
It's not the sound of our Akane or my stomach.
It will be the sound of thunder.
I hope you understand.
It rumbled, didn't it?
So...
I'd like to record this show under the circumstance that the name "Akane Sora" is a little bit backstage.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
I'd like to ask you a few questions.
First of all, what do you think of Uka-san?First of all, speaking of Uka-san
We are pleased to announce the release of our first major single Wonder Little Love on June 21!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much!
I'm sure you've held various release events in various places.
Looking back, how was it?
Well, it all happened very fast.
I've done a lot of releases since I started working here.
I've done a lot of releases since I started my career, but I think they were all done in the blink of an eye.
It was a release where I was able to meet a lot of different fans.
Did you go to many places?
Yes, I did. I went to Aichi, Osaka, and Hyogo.
I also went to Hyogo.
It was the first time for me to visit Lilybee in Hyogo, so I was very happy.
I see.
You also went to Okinawa at the beginning of July, right?
Yes, I did. It was my first time to go to Okinawa.
It was the first time for Uka, too.
It was the first time for me personally, too.
The sea was so beautiful!
Yes, it was.
Yes, it was. It was in Okinawa.
The ocean was very beautiful.
And we played at a live house in Okinawa.
The crowd was really excited.
Everyone was excited because it was in Okinawa.
And we were excited too.
It was so much fun!
Yay, I mean, yay!
Thank you very much.
What kind of tension is it that makes someone stop?
Yay!
Except for the live concerts and other work in Okinawa.
Did you have a chance to enjoy Okinawa?
Yes, I did. Um...
There is a beach called Secho BeachThere is a barbecue place called Secho Beach
There is a barbecue place called Secho Malibu.
We all go there to barbecue together.
We also went to Kokusai-dori to buy souvenirs.
We had a lot of free time.
We had a lot of free time, so we went to the places we wanted to go.
We had a lot of fun!
But since it was our first time in Okinawa
We had a great time.
I am glad that we were able to make great memories at the beginning of the summer.
I think so.
Mr. Shigeru, isn't he?
You update your Vlog and TikTok every day.
What is the secret to keep updating them everyday?
I don't have a secret to keep updating.
The most important thing is that I want to bring a good time to everyone.
If there is something that people can enjoy
If there is something to do every day
If there is something for everyone to enjoy every day, I hope it will be a reason to keep going.
If I keep doing this for so long, I don't want to stop.
I'm still doing my best to keep going.
To be able to keep doing something like this is like being in elementary school
When you were in elementary school, you did your homework in the summer vacation.
You are the type of person who does homework quickly and diligently?
No, I'm not.
You want me to say it with a bear face?
I like your smile.
I was always cold about homework in the second half of the year.
Then I say, "Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I'm the type of person who does it all at once.
Is that different from vlogging?
It's different.
I can do what I like and what I want to do.
I can do what I want to do, but what I don't want to do
What I don't want to do, I put off until later.
Is there anything you are putting off right now?Is there anything you are putting on the back burner right now?
What I'm putting off?
Surveys that have deadlines...
Because there is still a deadline.
I sometimes put them off a little bit because they are still due.
I was once told by a member to come back with a microphone.
I probably shouldn't do that, because it surprises a lot of staff members.
This article was sent to you courtesy of Hina-chan.
Thank you very much!